我们学会一件事  芝士
We learned one thing, Cheese:
啦啦队长跟强力火药不应该混在一起
Cheerleaders and high explosives don't mix.
你说的没错  麦克
You can say that again, Mac.
光靠我一个人是不行的 你是个天才
I couldn't have done it alone. You're a genius.
是吗  那我为什么无法
Oh, yeah? Well, how come
调整录影机的定时功能
I can't get my VCR to stop blinking 12:00?
你们觉得如何
What did you guys think?
-有电话  -我来接
- Hey, the phone. - I got it. I got it.
请等一下  乔伊是你妈妈
Hold on, please. Joey, it's your mom.
-是妈妈  -真好
- It's Mommy. - That's nice.
妈  你觉得如何
Ma. So, what did you think?
就
Well...
还好啦
...that was okay.
不是最棒的啦
It wasn't the best.
那是我看过最烂的东西
That was one of the worst things ever...
不光指的电视里播的
...and not just on TV.
-我们该说什么   -灯光还不错
- What should we say? - The lighting was okay.
不行  每次你都说灯光  这次我说
No, you don't. You got lighting last time. Lighting is mine.
服装是我的
I have costumes.
好  那就说明我只能说
Great. That means I'm stuck with:
"我们真的和荧幕上的大明星
"So we were watching you in there
坐在一起啊"
and you were sitting right here."
-你呢  -我不知道
- What you gonna do, Phoebe? - I don't know.
我没办法再骗他了  不  我
I can't lie to him again. Oh, no, I... No.
我就直接拿胸部压着他
I'm just gonna press my breasts up against him.
-然后什么都不说  -对
- And say nothing? - Yeah, that's right.
我爸妈很喜欢我的表演
My folks really liked it.
你们有什么看法
What did you guys think?
没那么好吧
It wasn't that good.
你知道你最喜欢的动物能说明很多你的特质吗
Do you think that your favorite animal says much about you?
它们背着我说我坏话啦
You mean behind my back?
你们一定不会相信  今天我经历了什么事
You'll never believe what happened to me today.
-我坐在办公室里  -伙计们
- I am sitting in my office... - You guys!
你们猜我的经纪人跟我说了什么
Guess what my agent just told me?
我这说话说到一半
I'm in the middle of a story here.
抱歉  你继续说吧
Sorry, you finish.
我坐在办公室里  你们猜谁走了进来
I'm sitting in my office, and guess who walks in.
我要参加两部电视剧的演出
I'm gonna be on two TV shows.
太棒了
That's great.
-乔伊  -你还没有说完吗
- Joey. - You werert finished?
对  "你猜谁进来了"就是故事的结局
Yeah, "Guess who walks into my office" is the end of my story.
罗夫·罗兰[著名设计师]走进我的办公室
Ralph Lauren walked into my office.
如果你想说别的事至少让我把我的事说完
If you're starting another story, at least let me finish mine.
我说的是同一件事
It's the same story.
还真长
It's really long.
罗夫走进来告诉我 他非常满意我的工作表现
Ralph just came in to tell me that he's so happy with my work...
他要我担任休闲服零售部
...that he wants me to be
新一人的销售经理
the new merchandising manager for Polo retail.
-买婚纱还有折扣吗  -有啊
- Still get a discount on wedding gowns? - Yeah.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
这确实是"我们的日子"啊
These really are the "Days of our lives."
-什么  -既然你问起
- What? - Well, since you ask...
他们要我回去演《我们的日子》
They want me back on Days of Our Lives.
还能大幅加薪
I get a big pay raise!
嘿
Oh, hey!
德雷克·拉莫瑞医生的双胞胎弟弟  史特莱科
I'll be playing Drake Ramoray's twin brother, Stryker.
我可以雇用专属助理
I get to hire my own assistant.
我起来太快  现在头很晕
I got a head rush from standing up too fast.
这份工作你做了四年
You were at this job four years?
-没错  -令人印象深刻啊  希尔达
- That's right. - This is all very impressive, Hilda.
最后一个问题
I just have one last question for you:
我表现得如何   还可以吧
How did I do? Was this okay?
-什么  -我从来没有面试过任何人
- What? - I've never interviewed anyone.
事实上我没有过手下
Actually I've never had anyone work for me.
我小时候家里有请佣人 但这完全不一样
When I was a kid we had a maid, but this isn't the same.
没错亲爱的  的确不一样
No, dear, it's not.
我知道
And I know that.
谢谢你来面试
Well, thank you so much for coming in.
-很高兴能见到你  -我也是
- It was nice to meet you. - Good meeting you.
好
All right.
我真专业
I'm a total pro.
你好
Hello.
你好  抱歉模特儿面试在走廊尽头的办公室
Hi, yes, I'm sorry. The models are down the hall.
我来面试助理的工作
Actually I'm here about the assistant job.
真的
Really?
好吧  我知道了  请坐
Okay, well, then, all right. Well, just have a seat there.
你叫什么名字
So, what's your name?
泰格·琼斯
Tag Jones.
继续
Go on.
就这样  那是我的全名
That's it. That's my whole name.
那是你的全名  当然
That's your whole name. Of course it is.
好了  我们来看一下
Okay, let's just have a look-see here.
我从来没有做过办公室工作
I haven't worked in an office before.
作经验不是很多
I don't have much experience...
你在胡说什么
What are you talking about?
你当过三年油漆工
You got three years painting houses...
有两个暑假在星期五餐厅打工
...two whole summers at TGI Friday's.
那些经验很烂  我知道
It's lame, I know.
但是我很有进取心  也愿意学习
But I'm a goal-oriented person, eager to learn...
请等一下
Just hold on a second, please.
这是人事部的要求  能麻烦你站起来吗
It's for human resources. Everybody has to. Would you stand up?
不不不
No, no, no.
嗨
Hey.
-总之我该走了  -好吧  再见
- Anyway, I should go. - Okay. Bye.
-嘿  亲爱的  -嘿  甜心
- Hey, sweetie. - Hi, sweetie.
你们嘀嘀咕咕在说什么
What was with all the whispering?
不能说  秘密
I can't tell you. It's a secret.
秘密  夫妻间不该有秘密的
Secret? Married people aren't supposed to have secrets.
我们深爱并且尊重彼此
We love and respect one another too much.
答案仍然是  不
But still, no.
我们应该对彼此坦诚
No, I'm serious. We should tell each other everything.
我就没有秘密
I don't have secrets from you.
真的吗  要不你来和我说下
Really? So why don't you tell me
罗斯在大三时在迪士尼乐园发生了什么事
what happened to Ross junior year at Disneyland.
不  我不能说
No, I can't do that.
如果你说  我就告诉你菲比说了什么
If you tell me, I'll tell you what Phoebe said.
-好吧  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
罗斯跟我一起去迪士尼乐园玩
So Ross and I are going to Disneyland.
我们在一家餐厅吃墨西哥卷饼
We stop at this restaurant for tacos.
其实那是一个人和一块铁板
When I say "Restaurant," I mean a guy,
还有他改装了的房车
a hibachi and the trunk of his car.
罗斯吃了十个墨西哥卷饼
So Ross has about 10 tacos.
总之我们在玩太空飞车时
Anyway, we're on Space Mountain
罗斯开始觉得不舒服
and Ross starts to feel a little iffy.
天啊  他吐了吗
Oh, my God. He threw up?
不  他从另一边把东西全拉了出来
No, he visited a town a little south of throw up.
菲比有什么秘密
What was Phoebe's secret?
南希·汤姆森
Nancy Thompson,
菲比以前按摩店的同事  被开除了
from Phoebe's old massage place, is getting fired.
就这样  我为了这个讲出了迪士尼的秘密
That's it? I gave up my Disneyland story for that?
没错  你输了  笨蛋
That's right. You lose, sucker!
你还是要娶我啊
Please still marry me.
钱德勒勒  你有助理吧
Chandler, you have an assistant, right?
她打电话来了吗
Did she call?
你告诉她我病了吧   每次都要说我生病了
You told her I was sick, right? Always tell her I am sick.
没  我只是不知道你怎么决定要雇用谁
No, I just don't know, how do you decide who to hire?
我把选择范围缩小到两个人
I have it down to two people.
一个的推荐信很棒  经验丰富
One has great references and a lot of experience.
-还有另一个男的  -他怎么了
- And then there's this guy...  - What about him?
我爱他
I love him.
他帅翻了  我好想哭
He's so pretty I want to cry.
我不知道该怎么办  告诉我该怎么做
I don't know what to do. Tell me what to do.
少来了  你知道自己该怎么办
Come on, you know what to do.
你得雇用第一个人
You hire the first one.
别因为他长得帅就雇他当助理
You don't hire assistants because they're cute.
你得考虑到他们的工作能力
You hire them because they're qualified.
我知道了  你说的有道理
I hear what you're saying. That makes a lot of sense.
我可以再说一件事吗
Can I just say one more thing?
快看多帅
Look how pretty.
让我看看
Let me see.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
但还是不行
Oh. But no.
不  你不能雇用他  因为那么做太不专业了
No. You can't hire him, because it's not professional.
这是给我的  对吧
This is for me, yes?
好吧  你说的对  明天我会雇用希尔达
Okay, you're right. I'll hire Hilda tomorrow.
那个又蠢又老  适合这份工作的希尔达
Dumb, old, perfect-for-the-job Hilda.
让我瞧瞧
Let me see this guy.
别让莫妮卡看到照片
Don't show this to Monica.
别告诉她我说"哇"
And don't tell her about the "Wow".
-嗨  乔伊 -嗨  泰瑞
- Hey, Joey. - Hey, Terry.
-很高兴能再跟你见面  -好久不见
- Nice to see you again. - It's been a while.
真有趣  这里的走廊看起来比以前小
Funny, these halls look smaller than they used to.
我们搬家了
It's a different building.
那么
So...
施特莱克是吧
...Stryker Ramoray, huh?
-我什么时候开始   -何不现在就开始呢
- When do I start? - How about right now?
好吧
Okay.
这是试镜的剧本
Here are the audition scenes.
试镜  我还以为你们决定让我饰演那个角色
Audition? I thought you were offering me the part.
你为什么会那么想
Why would you think that?
我演过德雷克医生 他是施特莱克的双胞胎哥哥
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray, Stryker's twin brother.
谁会比我长得更像我呢
Who looks more like me than me, right?
每个人都得参加试镜
Everybody has to audition.
你知道的  泰瑞  我真的不需要这么做
You know, Terry, I don't really need to do this.
我有自己的第四台电视剧
I got my own cable TV series...
跟机器人搭挡演出
...with a robot.
对不起  乔伊  这是规定
I'm sorry, Joey. That's the way it is.
那么
Well...
我猜你以为你很特别
...I guess you think you're pretty special.
你坐在漂亮的位于小走廊的办公室里
Sitting up here in your fancy, small-halled building...
要大明星在你面前使出浑身解数
...making stars jump through hoops for you.
你知道吗
Well, you know what?
我就是那个大明星
This is one star whose hoop...
我就是试演的   大明星试演
This is the star the hoop... This hoop...
我是德雷克医生
I was Dr. Drake Ramoray!
泰格  你在这里做什么
Hi, Tag. What are you doing here?
我来谢谢你  昨天没当着我的面笑我
I came to thank you for not laughing in my face yesterday.
我注意到你办公室里没有植物
I noticed there aren't any plants,
所以就帮你带盆植物过来
so I brought you your first...
你办公室里有植物
There is a plant in your office.
可以那么说
Kind of.
对
Right.
我猜我不应该在简历上写"注意力敏锐"
So I guess I shouldn't put "good at noticing stuff" on my resume.
-谢谢  -总之
- Thank you. - Anyway...
我猜你录取了别人
...l'm guessing you hired somebody.
那个嘛
Well...
懂了
Gotcha.
谢谢你愿意和我见面
Thanks again for meeting with me.
但我录取了你
But I hired you.
-什么  -对  你得到了这份工作
- What? - Yeah, you got the job.
-你是我的新助理  -真的吗
- You're my new assistant. - I am?
对
Yeah.
-我简直不敢相信  -我也是
- I can't believe it. - Me either.
首先我要你到楼下
First, I need you to go downstairs...
找一个叫希尔达的女人  要她回家去
...find a woman named Hilda and tell her to go home.
-嗨  -太好了  你回来了
- Hey. - Hey, good, you're home.
我想这要比听到"该死又是你"要好多了
Always nicer to hear than, "Oh, crap, you again."
甜心  我帮你准备了一个大惊喜
Hey, sweetie. I made you a surprise.
-是吗   -对  墨西哥卷饼
- Oh, yeah? - Yeah, tacos.
听完那个故事后 我一直都想吃墨西哥卷饼
Ever since that story I've had such a craving for them.
你听不懂那个故事吗
Did you not understand the story?
-嗨  -嗨  怎么了
- Hey. - Hey, what's up?
没事  我只是想知道晚餐要吃什么
Nothing. I'm just figuring out what to do for dinner.
那是什么   晚餐吗   你在做晚餐
Hey, what's that? Dinner stuff? You making dinner?
不
No.
你做了什么   墨西哥卷饼吗
What you got over there? Tacos?
不
No. No.
它们只是牛肉大饼
They're just... they're ground beef smileys.
那是墨西哥卷饼
Those are tacos.
失陪一下  墨西哥先生
Excuse me, Mr. Mexico.
没关系我不吃了  我还是不敢吃那玩意
Either way, I'll pass. Still can't eat those.
什么事那么好笑
What's so funny?
我没有笑
I'm not laughing.
你跟她说了
You told her!
南希·汤普森被开除了
Nancy Thompsors getting fired.
好吧  那时我食物中毒
Okay, okay. I had food poisoning.
我又没得选
It's not like I chose to do it!
我又没有说"怎样才会让飞车更好玩"
It's not like I said, "What would make this ride more fun?"
对  你说的对  抱歉  我不该笑的
Right. You're right, I'm sorry. I shouldn't be laughing.
我应该帮你先铺好报纸
I should be laying down papers for you.
-你怎么可以   - 我没得选择  我们要结婚了
- How could you tell you? - I had to. We're getting married.
夫妻不能有秘密
Married couples can't keep secrets from one to another.
我猜莫妮卡应该知道在大西洋城发生的事
I guess Monica should know about Atlantic City.
兄弟
Dude!
-发生了什么   -钱德勒跟我去酒吧
- What happened in Atlantic City?  - Chandler and I are in a bar...
你没有听到我说"兄弟"吗
Did you not hear me say, "Dude!"?
有个女孩跟钱德勒抛媚眼
...and this girl is making eyes at Chandler.
他走过去  一两分钟后我看到他们在接吻
So he goes over to her and after a minute or two I see them kissing.
现在你在想
Now, I know what you're thinking
"他可不是和酒吧里的女人鬼混的男人"
"He's not the type to go to bars and make out with girls."
你是对的  他的确不是那种
And you're right. He's not the type of guys...
在酒吧里的女人鬼混的男人
...to go to bars and make out with girls.
你跟男人接吻
You kissed a guy?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我得解释一下  那时很暗而且他长得很漂亮
In my defense, it was dark and he was a very pretty guy.
老妹  我笑得很大声
Oh, Mon, I laughed so hard...
你笑到又拉了一裤子
So hard we had to throw out your underwear again?
随便你  兄弟  你吻了男人
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hey.
希尔达适应的还好吧
How's Hilda? Is she working out?
我的新助理适应的很好  没错
Oh, my new assistant is working out. Yes.
她得到这份工作很高兴吧
She happy you gave her the job?
我的新助理非常高兴我雇用了我的新助理
My new assistant was very happy that I hired my new assistant.
喂
Hello.
嘿  你能等一下吗
Oh, hey! Can you hang on a second?
是《麦克芝士》的制作人打来的
It's the producers at Mac and Cheese,
允许我失陪一下
if you'll excuse me for a minute.
我没想到你会打来
Hey, funny you should call.
我正在看下星期的剧本
I was just looking over next week's script.
取消了
Canceled!
他们不播了
Like they're taking it off the air?
好吧  星期一见
All right. I'll see you Monday.
不再拍了
We're not even shooting them anymore?
好吧  再见
All right. Bye.
他们取消了《麦克芝士》
They canceled Mac and Cheese!
-我很抱歉  -我真的很遗憾  乔伊
- Sorry. - Sorry, Joey.
他们为什么要那么做   那部戏很棒对吧
Why would they do that? It was a good show, right?
你想说秘密吗   好吧念大学时
You want to tell secrets? Okay. In college...
罗斯都会穿护腿
...Ross used to wear leg warmers.
钱德勒参加模仿香草冰大赛还拿到了冠军
All right, Chandler entered a Vanilla Ice look-alike contest and won.
罗斯得了第四名  抱头痛哭
Ross came in fourth and cried!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
那很好笑吗   你觉得很好吗
Oh, is that funny? You find that funny?
或许钱德勒也应该知道你的秘密
Maybe Chandler should know your secrets too.
我已经告诉他一切了  你给我闭嘴
I already told him everything. You shush!
有一次她被罚不准吃晚餐
Once Monica was sent to bed without dinner...
结果她吃掉了她用意大利面做的珠宝盒
...so she ate the macaroni off a jewelry box she'd made.
罗斯每个星期六晚上都待在家里看《黄金女郎》
Ross stayed home every Saturday night to watch Golden Girls.
莫妮卡到十三岁才会看表
Monica couldn't tell time until she was 13.
有些人就是学不会
It's hard for some people!
那当然
Of course it is.
-钱德勒曾穿我的内裤去上班  -嘿
- Chandler wore my underwear to work once! - Hey!
对不起  我想不出来  罗斯还有什么糗事
I'm sorry, I couldn't think of any more for Ross.
在大学时有一次钱德勒喝醉了
In college, Chandler got drunk...
他跟打扫房间的清洁妇上床
...and slept with the lady who cleaned our dorm.
那是你
That was you.
随便  兄弟  你吻了个男人
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
这种事怎么会发生在我身上
How could this happen to me?
昨天我演出两部电视剧  今天我什么都没有
Yesterday I had two TV shows. Today I got nothing.
等一下  《我们的日子》呢
Wait a minute, what happened to Days of our Lives?
他们可能有点生我的气
Well, they might be a little mad at me over there.
发生了什么事
What happened?
或许我有点生气  也许我让他们去见鬼了
Well, maybe I got a little upset, and maybe I told them where they could go.
乔伊  你为什么要那么做
Joey, why would you do that?
因为他们要我试镜
Because! They wanted me to audition.
你可是个演员  那么做太过份了
You? An actor? That's madness!
瑞秋·格林办公室
Rachel Greers office.
泰格
Tag.
嗨  谁打电话找我
Hi, who was that?
没有人  我只是在练习
Nobody. I was just practicing.
真的吗
Really?
-嗨  -嗨  瑞秋·格林办公室
- Hi. - Hi, Rachel Greers office.
你一定是希尔达
You must be Hilda.
他是泰格  这位是菲比
He's Tag. This is Phoebe.
菲比  你能进来一下吗
Phoebe, can I see you for a sec?
菲比
Phoebe.
-这个名字很不错  -你喜欢吗
- That's a great name. - Oh, you like that?
你应该听听我的电话号码
You should hear my phone number.
好吧  我们马上回来
Okay. We'll be right back.
你为了自己雇用了个大帅哥  对吧
So you hired yourself a little treat, did you?
我知道这看起来不妙  但是我告诉你
I know how it looks, but I am telling you...
你不能潜规则你的助理
You can't get involved with your assistant.
我知道
I know that,
我知道雇用他不是明智之举
and I know hiring him was not the smartest thing I've ever done.
但从现在开始  我发誓我们之间是纯公事
But I'm telling you from this moment, I swear this is strictly professional.
-对  -嘿  瑞秋
- Yes. - Hey, Rachel.
嗨
Hi.
你助理很帅  什么背景啊
Cute assistant. What's his story?
-他  -是同性恋吗   对
- Is he... - Gay? Yeah.
嘿  泰瑞
Hey, Terry.
是乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我很惊讶像你这样的大人物能穿过我们的小走廊
Surprised your big head could fit through our small halls.
-我得走了  乔伊  -等一下  泰瑞  听我说
- I gotta go, Joey.  - Wait, Terry! Look.
之前的事我抱歉
I'm really sorry about before.
我是个白痴  以为自己很大牌不必试镜
I was an idiot, thinking I'm too big to audition for you.
-再给我一次机会  -我办不到
- Give me another chance. - I can't.
等一下  泰瑞  求求你
Wait, Terry, please!
听着  我失去了我另一份工作
Look, I just lost my other job, okay?
你不知道我多需要这部剧
You have no idea how much I need this.
求你帮帮我
Please, help me out.
我们是老朋友了
For old times' sake.
这家伙昏迷了五年  他已经没希望了
This guy's been in a coma for five years. It's hopeless.
不会的  施特莱克医生擅长施展奇迹
It's not. Dr. Stryker Ramoray is a miracle worker.
他来了
Here he comes.
早安
Good morning.
德雷克我是你弟弟施特莱克  你听到了吗
Drake, it's your brother, Stryker. Can you hear me?
卡
And cut.
我又回来了  宝贝
I'm back, baby!
我要解释
You know, in my defense...
意大利面上没有珠宝而且我用的胶水很少
...there was no glitter on the macaroni and very little glue.
我的解释是那个清洁妇勾引我
And in my defense, the cleaning lady came on to me.
-你现在会看时间了吗   -会
- Do you have trouble telling time now? - No.
快速反应  现在几点了
Quick, what time is it?
不知道  吻男人的时间吗
I don't know, time to kiss a guy maybe?
你在笑什么   尿布宝宝
What are you laughing at, Pampers?
你知道我说夫妻
You know when I said married people...
应该分享一切  不可以有秘密吗
...should share everything and not have any secrets?
-怎么了   -那太蠢了我们千万别那么做
- Yeah. - Yeah, that was stupid. Let's not do that.
一点都没错
Absolutely.
我们不该把彼此的秘密再告诉其他人
We should keep the stuff we told each other secret from everyone else.
一点都没错
Yeah, definitely.
好吧  对不起
Okay. If you'll excuse me...
我要跟不知道
...l'm gonna hang out
太空飞车事件的人去玩了
with people who don't know the Space Mountain story.
-我建议你别去找菲比  -天啊
- Then I'd steer clear of Phoebe. - Man!
倒不是说你会找我同事啦
Not that you would,
但是他们你也别找了
but I wouldn't hang out with the guys at my office.
嗨
Hi.
-你有空吗   -当然  有什么事吗
- Do you have a minute? - Sure. What's up?
午餐的时候  有两个人想约我出去
I got asked out twice today while I was at lunch...
他们都是男人
...by guys.
-真的吗   -对
- Really? - Yeah.
你告诉别人我是同性恋吗
Did you tell someone that I was gay?
你不希望别人知道吗
Oh, did you not want people to know that?
我不是同性恋 我特别不希望你以为我是同性恋
I'm not gay. I especially wouldn't want you to think I was gay.
为什么
Why is that?
-我想我不该说的  -你说吧
- I don't think I should say. - Oh, you can say.
别这样  我不希望你有事不敢告诉我
Come on, I don't want you to feel like you can't tell me things.
-好吧  -好吧
- Okay. - Okay.
-那个  -是的
- Well... - Yeah.
我想约你朋友菲比出去
I'd love to ask out your friend Phoebe.
是啊  她是同性恋
Yeah, she's gay.